sutree.com 2008-06-19

# Privacy Policy, SuTree.com

SuTree is committed to making every possible effort to protect the privacy   
of its users. The following Privacy Policy includes information regarding the use and disclosure of users' information that is collected by SuTree.   
This Privacy Policy is presented here in order to help our users decide whether they agree with SuTree’s practices.   
Your use of SuTree and any personal information you may provide to SuTree remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.   
By using, accessing the Website, or uploading content to the Website,   
you agree to the collection and use of your personal information (as hereunder described), in accordance with the terms and conditions set in this Privacy Policy and in the Website's Terms of Use. SuTree has the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is the user's responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes.   
Your use of the Website following any change of this Privacy Policy will be considered as your acceptance of its revised terms.   
Important notice: any link, video clip, image, or other content posted by users on SuTree becomes published public content.   
Collection and Use of Information  
1\. Users are requested to provide certain personal information  
(such as name and  email address) to SuTree when choosing to participate in  
various activities such as: adding links, uploading videos, creating personal pages (My SuTree), asking or answering questions, creating a course,   
commenting on a video, subscribing to newsletters, or other activities that require registration.  
2\. When you visit SuTree, cookie or cookies - small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - may be sent to your computer.  These cookies uniquely identify your browser. We use both session and persistent  cookies.  
Session cookies are temporary and disappear after the browser is closed. Persistent cookies are cookies that remain in your computer after you close the browser. These may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to eWebsite.   
It is possible to reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please note that some features of the Website may not function at all or not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.  
3\. When you use SuTree, our servers automatically record certain information that  
your web browser sends whenever you visit the Website, known as: Log File   Information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet  Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request etc. SuTree may collect or receive this log file information.  
4\. The information collected by SuTree is used to operate and improve the features, content, and offerings presented to you by the Website; to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to communicate with you; to conduct research about your use of the Website, etc.  
5\. Important notice: SuTree may use your personal information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertiser. However, none of your personal information will be disclosed to third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. Our business partners and advertisers will only receive aggregate data about SuTree's users.  
6\. Notwithstanding the foregoing, users' personal information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures. Furthermore, SuTree may transfer personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of the Website, in which case the information could become subject to a different Privacy Policy.  
7\. Any personal information orv video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in comments, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your nickname (not your full name or your email address) will be displayed to other users when you add links, upload videos, or comment on videos.   
8\. We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.  
9\. You might be given the opportunity to receive offers from third parties  
which are not affiliated with SuTree. Should you decide to accept these offers,  
we will provide, with your consent, your information to the third party. However,  
please note that any information users give to another party is governed by the  
rules of that party's Privacy Policy, which may differ from our Privacy Policy.  
SuTree will not be responsible for information given to other parties. Please review  
their privacy policies prior to providing any information to them.  
10\. We may use Web beacons - electronic images, also known as single-pixel gifs that allow us to count users and to deliver co-branded services. Newsletters and promotional e-mail messages from SuTree may also include these Web beacons. This helps us count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information, but rather they are used to compile aggregated statistics about our Website usage. Data Security We are committed to use reasonable physical and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. Nevertheless, it is impossible to ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to SuTree and you do so at your own risk. In case we find a security systems breach, we may notify you electronically or post a notice on our site so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronicnotice) you should notify us here.
